It seems that the more days Didi spends in prison, the more alleged victims
Parece ser que conforme más días va pasando Didi dentro de la prisión más presuntas víctimas se
are daring to come out to report the alleged shady or even criminal events that they had
están atreviendo a salir a denunciar los presuntos sucesos turbios o incluso criminales que habrían
experienced with Cindy Dicom. And you already know that during the time that Didi has been in prison
vivido con Cindy dicom Y es que ya sabéis que durante el tiempo que Didi ha estado campando
at ease around the planet doing whatever he wanted as if the planet had no laws
a sus anchas por el planeta haciendo lo que le daba la gana como si el planeta no tuviera leyes
for him. Well, in fact, I would dare to say that even today there are still many people
para él Bueno de hecho yo me atrevería a firmar que incluso a día de hoy todavía hay mucha gente
who do not dare to open their mouths and who prefer stay on the sidelines, unlike the
que no se atreve abrir el pico y que prefiere mantenerse al margen a diferencia del caso de
Jeffrey Epting case in which more famous people came out to speak and raise their voices in this It seems that there is
Jeffrey epting en el que más famosos salieron a hablar alzar la voz en este Parece ser que hay
more fear that they have more respect for this guy, the point is that now it seems that people are
más miedo que a este tío le tienen más respeto la cuestión es que ahora Parece que la gente se
feeling a little more sure about the fact that Didy is in prison and they won't let him out despite
va sintiendo un poco más segura con esto de que didy está en prisión y no le dejan salir a pesar
the multiple agreements he has tried with the judges offering a lot of millions a
de los múltiples acuerdos que ha intentado con los jueces ofreciendo un montón de millones un
lot of conditions that he is willing to accept later during the video I will tell you about them but
montón de condiciones que está dispuesto a aceptar luego durante el vídeo os la iré comentando pero
for example, even selling his private Je so that they do not understand a risk of flight and it is worth nothing to
por ejemplo incluso vender su Je privado para que no entiendan un riesgo de fuga y nada les vale a
the judges. In other words, he is not going to get out of prison and in fact it is stipulated that he could be sentenced in a
los jueces O sea no va a salir de prisión y de hecho se estipula que podrían condenarlo en una
range of between 15 years and life imprisonment for What in this video I am going to tell you about the latest
horquilla de entre 15 años y cadena perpetua por lo que en este vídeo os voy a comentar las últimas
things that are coming out and new alleged victims who are raising their voices and shouting
cosas que están saliendo y nuevas presuntas víctimas que están alzando la voz y poniendo
to the heavens with the atrocities that have happened with didcom. We are also going to talk about
el grito en el cielo con las barbaridades que han pasado con didcom también vamos a hablar sobre
an alleged intimate video with the who could be threatening Justin Bieber or at least have him
un presunto vídeo íntimo con el que podría estar amenazando a Justin Bieber o por lo menos tenerlo
coionia welcome one more day to my channel I'm Javi oliveira if you didn't know me and you
coionia bienvenidos un día más a mi canal Soy Javi oliveira si no me conocías y te
like this topic I invite you to subscribe because here we comment on all
gusta esta temática te invito a que te suscribas porque aquí comentamos todo
the salsa of the famous youtubers of the TV Stars everything viral
el salseo de los youtubers de los famosos de las Estrellas de la tele todo lo viral
here you will find out better than anywhere So like subscribe share and
aquí te vas a enterar mejor que en ningún lado Así que like suscribirte compartir y
all those things that are free make yourself comfortable And let's go to the Leon before getting into the matter
todas esas cosas que son gratis ponte cómodo Y vamos al Leon antes de entrar en materia
the first thing I would like to update is the situation that Didi is having inside the
lo primero que me gustaría actualizar es la situación que está teniendo Didi dentro de la
prison at the moment and this morning his lawyer came out to give some statements to the
prisión en estos momentos y es que esta mañana salió su abogado a dar unas declaraciones a la
press. He has answered few questions but we will know something after spending the whole morning with him,
prensa ha respondido pocas preguntas pero algo sabremos después de pasar toda la mañana con él
one of the things he has answered the lawyer It is on
una de las cosas a las que ha contestado el abogado Es sobre
the subject of the thousand bottles of drinking lubricant that were found in one of
el tema de los mil botes de lubricante para beber que se encontraron en una de
the mansions that he justifies by saying that Americans usually buy in bulk
las mansiones que justifica diciendo que los estadounidenses suelen comprar al por mayor
do cons ads you know getan to that someh sex is aad Thing Because If It was And what do you want me
do cons ads you know getan to that someh sex is aad Thing Because If It was Y qué queréis
to tell you? I have my doubts that Cindy c Daddy needs to buy and get offers at
que os diga tengo yo mis dudas de que a Cindy c Daddy le haga falta comprar y pillar ofertas en
the supermarket where she has to buy a lot to save a little on the price but well
el super en el que tenga que comprar un montón para ahorrarse un poco del precio pero bueno
, it is true that simply the The fact that it is baby lubricant would not mean that it is not
sí que es verdad que simplemente el hecho de que sea lubricante para bebés No querría decir que no
being used for consensual sex. This seems to me to be a somewhat curious piece of information, but not the most
se esté utilizando para un sexo consentido Este me parece un dato medio curioso pero no el más
important one that we have of all the indications and accusations against Paz Dadi, which
importante que tenemos de todos los indicios y las acusaciones a Paz dadi este casi que se
could almost be justified, although The other strong situation that is occurring in the last few
podría justificar aunque sea un poco raro la otra situación fuerte que se está dando en las últimas
hours is a bit strange. It is about Kim Potter's diary. You already know that Kim Potter is one of
horas Es sobre el diario de Kim Potter ya sabéis que Kim Potter es una de las parejas más longevas
Cindy Dicom's longest-lived couples. She was his wife and mother of several of his children. He had a quite intermittent relationship
de Cindy dicom fue su esposa y madre de varios de sus hijos tuvo una relación bastante intermitente
between 1994 and 2007 where they even stood still for years before returning sincerely in front of
entre 1994 y 2007 donde incluso estuvieron parado durante años antes de volver sinceramente de cara
the public at least They have always had a good relationship even after breaking up the relationship one
al público por lo menos Siempre han tenido buena relación incluso luego de romper la relación una
of the last publications of this woman was congratulating him as a father but yes It is true
de las últimas publicaciones de esta mujer fue felicitándolo como padre pero sí que es verdad
that there are many people who have certain conspiracies about the reason for his death
que hay mucha gente que tiene como ciertas conspiraciones por el motivo de su muerte
and that is that in 2018, at only 47 years old, he died due to pneumonia and many people
y es que en el año 2018 con tan solo 47 años falleció a causa de una neumonía y mucha gente
suspected that this was something quite strange because there was talk that He was about to
sospechaba que esto era algo Bastante extraño porque se hablaba de que estaba a punto de
release a book with all his memories telling a lot of things he had experienced among others in
sacar un libro con todas sus memorias contando un montón de cosas que había vivido entre otras en
constances that didy Had something to do with the Death of his ex Partner and the
constances that didy Had something to do with the Death of his ex Partner and the
mother to his children Woman named Kim Porter Now What happened was She
mother to his children Woman named Kim Porter Now What happened was She
mysteriously Died of pneumonia at the Age of 47 not the typical way that a 47y old goes
mysteriously Died of pneumonia at the Age of 47 not the typical way that a 47y old goes
out especially Just When They are about to publish a Tell all Book about their very Famous
out especially Just When They are about to publish a Tell all Book on their very Famous
That's What happened to Kim She Died of pneumonia at the Age of 47 years old well
That's What happened to Kim She Died of pneumonia at the Age of 47 years old well
Guess What It was Just announced Yesterday that kim's porter's Book is Being published It's a
Guess What It was Just announced Yesterday that kim's porter's Book is Being published It's a
60 page Book entitled kim's Lost words claims to be a Collection of the Diaries of Kim Porter the
60 page Book entitled kim's Lost words claims to be a Collection of the Diaries of Kim Porter the
mother of diddy's children and It was leaked by her Friends In The Book Porter allegedly
mother of diddy's children and It was leaked by her Friends In The Book Porter allegedly
recounts discovering and making copies of the tapes that didy made of himself having with
recounts discovering and making copies of the tapes that didy made of himself having with
young Boys that he was managing including an alleged tape involving an 18-year old
young Boys that he was managing including an alleged tape involving an 18-year old
I am not going to deny that it could seem suspicious although I think that everything here also has a tinge
no voy a negar que podría parecer sospechoso aunque creo que también todo aquí tiene un tinte
of Conspiracy but well yes it could be suspicious and even more so taking into account all the data that
de Conspiración pero bueno sí sospechoso podría ser y más teniendo en cuenta todos los datos que
Today we have all the things that we know that this man was capable of doing And he is capable of
tenemos hoy todas las cosas que conocemos que este hombre fue capaz de hacer Y es capaz de
doing how far he is able to go to achieve And manage to impose what he says or silence the
hacer hasta dónde capaz de llegar por conseguir Y lograr imponer lo que él diga o callar a la
crowd, we will see what they say but for now the children deny it is seeing any
peña veremos a ver qué es lo que dicen pero de momento los hijos lo niegan est viendo alguna
part of those supposed leaked memories in a book and It seems that the Source is Chris
parte de esas supuestas memorias filtradas en un libro y Parece ser que la Fuente es Chris
Chris tot is a producer who claimed to be a good friend of Kim Potter and one of the few to whom
Chris tot es un productor que decía ser muy amigo de Kim Potter y uno de los pocos a los que
it is assumed that she happened his memoirs in a ucb so that he could read them before publishing them It seems
se supone que ella le pasó sus memoria en un ucb para que él las leyera antes de publicarlas Parece
that this man has decided to publish them taking advantage of now that Didi is in jail And
ser que este hombre pues ha decidido publicarlas aprovechando ahora que Didi está en la cárcel Y
well, the truth is that I have to say that it looks quite credible Although it is true that
bueno pues la verdad que tengo que decir que se ve bastante creíble Aunque sí que es verdad que
There is no type of proof to prove its veracity. I organized parties that were nothing more than
no hay ningún tipo de prueba para demostrar su veracidad organizaba fiestas que no eran más que
a fancy name for [__] and everyone wanted to participate. The memories claimed that
un nombre elegante para [__] y todo el mundo quería participar afirmaban las memorias de por
we not only had threesomes but also exchanged partners. Our
no solo hacíamos tríos sino que también intercambiábamos parejas nuestra vida
sex life was crazy. But I was able to do things with Sean that I would never have been able to do with a
sexual era una locura pero pude hacer cosas con sean que nunca habría podido hacer con un hombre
heterosexual man. In those supposed memoirs he told how it was the first time that Didi hit him, which
heterosexual en esas supuestas memorias contaba Cómo fue la primera vez que Didi le golpeó que
apparently was when he slapped her with his open hand in the face after she
al parecer fue que le pegó un guantazo con la mano abierta en la cara después de que ella
rejected him. use a harness with a dildo then immediately He apologized to her claiming that
rechazara usar un arnés con un consolador luego inmediatamente Se disculpó con ella alegando que
he had been a horny and describes many other episodes of attacks and threats but the most
había sido un calentón y describe muchos otros episodios de agresiones y amenazas pero lo más
talked about is the following some of the tapes had things that he would never have expected
comentado es lo siguiente algunas de las cintas tenían cosas que nunca hubiera esperado las
gay parties are one thing but the young boys like two hip hop stars who were previously
fiestas gay son una cosa pero los chicos jóvenes como dos estrellas de hip hop que antes eran
representatives of Didi and La Estrella Del Pop who was 18 years old at the time. I would never have imagined it.
representantes de Didi y La Estrella Del Pop que entonces tenía 18 años Nunca lo hubiera imaginado
I don't know how you understand this but people have taken it for something quite obvious and that is a
yo no sé cómo entendéis ustedes esto pero la gente lo ha tomado por algo Bastante obvio y que es una
clear reference to Justin Bieber. It also seems that the editor of this supposed memoir
Clara referencia a Justin Bieber además Parece ser que el editor de esta supuestas memorias le
has told Daily Mail that apart from having had the USB, he has also had proof that King
ha dicho a Daily mail que aparte de haber tenido es USB también ha tenido pruebas de que King le
sent him to some friends because how he used makeup to cover up the bruises and Well, what I think is
envió a algunos amigos pues cómo se maquillaba para tapar los golpes y Bueno lo que yo creo que
going to give the title to this video is surely the supposed video of Didi with a
le va a dar título a este vídeo seguramente es el supuesto vídeo de Didi con una estrella del
teenage pop star that I can't think of anyone else other than Justin Bieber, it is certain
pop adolescente que a mí no se me ocurre otro tampoco que no sea Justin Bieber sea ciencia
that Didi's sex video with the teenage pop star has been introduced to
cierta que el video sexual de Didi con la estrella pop adolescente ha sido presentado a estudios de
Hollywood studios by is inter and What has Come on the heels of This is people unearthing videos of
Hollywood por is inter and What has Come on the heels of This is people unearthing videos of
Justin Bieber Justin Bieber at didy parties Now Justin Bieber was obviously extremely young when
Justin Bieber Justin Bieber at didy parties Now Justin Bieber was obviously extremely young when
he entered the Industry extremely innocent when he entered the Industry an Industry that he did
he entered the Industry extremely innocent when he entered the Industry an Industry that he did
not quite understand as a boy Who Just knew How to sing and play the guitar and Just did both of
not quite understand as a boy Who Just knew How to sing and play the guitar and Just did both of
Those things on Youtube then He was scooped up and suddenly he was A Part Of people like
Those things on Youtube then He was scooped up and suddenly he was A Part Of people like
didy going after him and saying Hey man Why won you pick up my phone calls It's actually
didy going after him and saying Hey man Why won you pick up my phone calls It's actually
a rather curious clip that people comment on a lot and it's this one that I'm going to put
hay un clip bastante curioso que la gente comenta mucho y es este que voy a poner a
below where It seems that between goodbyes and hugs he worries a lot about touching
continuación donde Parece ser que entre despedidas y abrazos se preocupa mucho como de toquetear
to Justin Bieber and It seems that he would be recording and making sure that he does not have a
a Justin Bieber y Parece ser que estaría registrando y asegurándose de que no lleva un
microphone esing to leak peace Daddy's information. So if Daddy was so interested
micrófono esing filtrar la información de paz Daddy Entonces si Daddy estuviera tan interesado
in recording to see if he has a microphone in case he has recorded something from this meeting, then surely
en registrar a ver si tiene un micrófono por si ha grabado algo de esta reunión pues seguramente
because they have met to talk about something shady or because who knows what happened in
porque han quedado para hablar algo turbio o porque vete tú a saber qué ha pasado en
the event that the theory that he was feeling to see if there is a bug was true,
el caso de que fuera verdad la teoría de que estuviera palpando para ver si hay un micro
I don't know how to tell me what you thought just a few hours ago Kim Potter's children and Didi have
no sé decirme ustedes qué pensáis hace apenas unas horas Los hijos de Kim Potter y Didi han
come out to deny this book that is going to come out with those memories, saying that it is absolutely false
salido a desmentir este libro que va a salir con esas memorias diciendo que es absolutamente falso
that her mother has never written anything like that, that she has not left any type of memories anywhere
que su madre nunca haya escrito nada de eso que no ha dejado ningún tipo de memorias en
and that obviously, in case it is necessary to emphasize it, death of his mother at
ningún lado y que evidentemente por si hace falta recalcarlo la muerte de su madre a los
47 years old was something completely natural due to pneumonia and that anyone who invents
47 años fue algo completamente natural a causa de la neumonía y que cualquier persona que se
the opposite or any type of thing in those memoirs is obviously not his friend,
invente lo contrario o cualquier tipo de cosa en esas memorias evidentemente no es su amigo
referring to krot, that is, it seems that the children are not Happy with what this
refiriéndose a krot o sea Parece ser que los hijos no están contentos con esto que este
producer is doing, they have asked for respect for their mother's memory and Amazon has removed the
productor está haciendo han pedido respeto para la memoria de su madre y Amazon ha retirado el
book after they requested it. It is true that the last thing she published on her
libro después de que ellos lo pidieran Es verdad que lo último que ella publicó en su cuenta de
Instagram account was this photograph congratulating her ex or Whether it's Didi for her birthday and stating
Instagram fue esta fotografía felicitando a su ex o sea a Didi por su cumpleaños y afirmando
that she feels proud of how she is as a father, I'll tell you one thing, or whether a man can be the worst
que se siente orgullosa de cómo es como padre os digo una cosa o sea un hombre puede ser la peor
person in the world with people or be a terrible self who knows a thousand things and then maybe it's a good
persona del mundo con la gente o ser un terrible yo que sé mil cosas y luego a lo mejor es un buen
father I don't know, I think one thing doesn't rule out the other. We have seen so many hurtful and
padre No sé creo que una cosa no descarta la otra hemos visto circular tantos humores hirientes y
false humor circulating about our parents, Kim Porter and Sean Coms' relationship, as well as the tragic
falsos sobre nuestros padres la relación de Kim Porter y sean coms como así como sobre el trágico
death of our mother that we feel the need to speak out. Claims that
fallecimiento de de nuestra madre que sentimos la necesidad para hablar las afirmaciones de que
our mother wrote a book are simply false, she did not and anyone who claims
nuestra madre escribió un libro son simplemente falsas ella lo hizo no y cualquiera que afirme
to have a manuscript is misrepresenting themselves. Additionally, please understand that any so-called
tener un manuscrito es tergiversando a sí mismos además por favor comprenda que cualquier supuesto
friend who speaks on behalf of our mother or her family is not a friend nor does she have her best
amigo que hable en nombre de nuestra madre o su familia no es amiga ni tiene sus mejores
interests at heart our lives were shattered when we lost our mother
intereses en el fondo nuestras vidas quedaron destrozadas cuando perdimos a nuestra madre
she was our world and nothing has been the same since she passed away although it has been incredibly
ella era nuestro mundo y nada ha sido igual desde que ella falleció si bien ha sido increíblemente
difficult to reconcile how she could be taken from us too soon the cause of her death has
difícil conciliar como ella podría ser quitado de nosotros demasiado pronto la causa de su muerte ha
been established for a long time there was no foul play Grieving is a lifelong process and
sido establecido desde hace mucho tiempo no hubo juego sucio El Duelo es un proceso de por vida y
we ask that everyone respect our request for peace as we continue to deal with his loss
pedimos que todos respeten nuestro petición de paz a medida que continuamos lidiando con su pérdida
each day we are deeply saddened that the world has given such a spectacle which
cada día estamos profundamente entristecidos de que el mundo haya dado un espectáculo de lo que
has been the most tragic event of our lives our mother should be remembered for what a beautiful
ha sido el evento más trágico de nuestras vidas nuestro la madre debe ser recordada por lo hermoso
strong kind and loving woman she was her memory should not be tainted by horrible
fuerte amable y mujer amorosa que era su memoria no debería estar manchada por horribles teorías
Conspiracy theories We ask everyone to respect our mother Kim Porter and keep her legacy
de Conspiración Les pedimos a todos que respeten a nuestra madre Kim Porter y mantenga su legado
in high esteem so that she can rest in peace is what she deserves we love you and we miss you
en alta estima para que pueda descansar en paz es lo que ella se merece te amamos y te extrañamos
mommy kin Cristian Jessi and delila the fact that there are videos found is a fact in one of the
mami kin Cristian Jessi y delila lo de que hay vídeos encontrados es un hecho en uno de los
raids you can find it in any of the news that talk about this topic. In fact,
allanamientos lo podéis encontrar en cualquiera de las noticias que hablan de este tema de hecho
we have a first video where I go into depth about these investigations. Well, several videos. In
tenemos un primer vídeo donde entro en profundidad sobre estas investigaciones bueno varios vídeos de
fact, I recommend that you go to the playlist that is on the Channel. In fact,
hecho os recomiendo que os metáis en la lista de reproducción que hay en el Canal de hecho
if you want to know all the information about this topic, but It is not yet known what type of videos
si queréis saber toda la información sobre este tema pero no se sabe todavía Qué tipo de vídeos
they are, exactly which Hollywood stars they involve and more than doubts. Well, I think that
son exactamente a qué estrellas de Hollywood involucran y más que dudas Pues yo creo que eso
would explain the silence of many. Yes, it is quite strange, eh, or the fact that with the case of
explicaría el silencio de muchos Sí es bastante extraño eh o sea el hecho de que con el caso de
Johnny Depp and Amber for example of Jeffrey there is also something but especially in the case of John
Johnny Depp y Amber por ejemplo de Jeffrey estin también algo pero sobre todo en el caso de John
for example a lot of actors and hyper mega powerful people spoke out. They had no
de por ejemplo un montón de actores y personas hiper mega poderosas se pronunciaron No tuvieron
problems in positioning themselves while we were following the case we saw how there were people who
problemas en posicionarse mientras que estuvimos siguiendo el caso veíamos como había gente que
stopped following Amber or that put out statements against Johnny but in this case not in this
dejaba de seguir a Amber o que ponía comunicados en contra de Johnny pero en este caso no en este
case it is that they are trying to tiptoe and there is an overwhelming silence the only one who gets wet
caso es que están intentando pasar de puntillas y hay un silencio abrumador el único que se moja
but like with two [ __ ] is f zen or 50 zen as I call it Well, he has already reached an
pero en plan con dos [__] es f zen o 50 zen como yo lo llamo que bueno ya ha llegado a un
agreement with Netflix in which he is preparing a documentary that I believe is going to be the most
acuerdo con Netflix en el que está preparando un documental que yo creo que va a ser el más
complete that talks about this topic where he is going to expose Paz Daddy. We are talking about what
completo que hable de este tema dónde va a exponer a Paz Daddy estamos hablando de que
fyen apart from having a lot of Manía for him. He has been investigating Paz for years with private investigators
fyen aparte de de tenerle mucha Manía Lleva años con investigadores privados investigando a Paz
Daddy, that's why I tell you that I think I'm not wrong when I think that this documentary is going to be the most
Daddy por eso os digo que creo que no me equivoco cuando pienso que este documental va a ser el más
complete. There are others like Eminen who have said things in their songs. What happens is that you already know this
completo hay otros como eminen que han dicho cosas en sus canciones lo que pasa es que ya sabéis este
thing they have, not that they are supposed to rap lyrics or bullshit in music because
rollo que tienen no que se supone que las letras de rap o las tiraderas en la música pues como que
they don't have the same weight as when they are said when they are said outside of a song, I mean, I don't
no tienen el mismo peso que cuando se dicen cuando se dicen fuera de una canción o sea es que no le
see the point, we have discussed this, and I have even had debates on my channel with People from this
veo el sentido esto lo hemos discutido eh incluso he tenido debates en mi canal con gente de esta
Cock Battles didn't say that it's good that it was a bullfight and in the battles
de Las batallas de gallos no que afirmaban que bueno que la tiraera y en las batallas
Well, it's fiction to say things to each other But well, I see it as nonsense I see that what you say
Pues que es ficción decirse las cosas Pero bueno yo lo veo una chorrada Yo veo que lo que digas
in a song is that you are interpreting it in some way your feelings or what you think
en una canción Es que estás interpretando de alguna manera tus sentimientos o lo que piensas
let's see I hope to pronounce it correctly Nike hiton is this singer that you are seeing on the screen
a ver espero pronunciarlo bien Nike hiton es esta cantante que estáis viendo en pantalla
well she is very well known she is very popular she narrated a pretty strong episode I mean this episode
que bueno es muy conocida es muy popular narró un episodio bastante fuerte o sea este episodio
is very very very bad I don't know Even if a youtuber tells me You can censor the editor is going to try
es muy muy muy tocho no sé Incluso si youtuber me lo puede censurar el editor va a intentar
to put a little filter on sensitive words But well basically there was non-consensual touching
poner un poco de filtro a las palabras sensibles Pero bueno básicamente hubo manoseo sin consen
by did with an executive producer after trying to give them a drink with
por parte de did con un productor ejecutivo después de intentar darles una bebidas con
drugs in it that ended with her running out of the place Although
drogas en ella que acabó con ella Saliendo corriendo del lugar Aunque
yes it is true that I do not understand why this girl has not demanded for the moment
sí que es verdad que no entiendo por esta chica no ha demandado de momento
to do Reach for my phone And I Start to type and with takes The Phone out of my
to do Reach for my phone And I Start to type and con takes The Phone out of my
hand and He's like Who are you texting like you don't need to text anyone like
hand and He's like Who are you texting like you don't need to text anyone like
we're having a Party And I was like Okay and he like puts it on One of the speakers
we're having a Party And I was like Okay and he like puts it on One of the speakers
and I'm like fuck Now What do I do um like I I don't I don't know what to do and I see my
and I'm like fuck Now What do I do um like I I don't I don't know what to do and I see my
manager take a sip and I'm like fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck Now What do I do and then I see
manager take a sip and I'm like fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck Now What do I do and then I see
her Take another sip two sips out have this Little vodka Cranberry Cup and I'm like Oh
her Take another sip two sips out have this Little vodka Cranberry Cup and I'm like Oh
What do I What do I do two sips And I watch her Face flush And All of a sudden like I look over
What do I What do I do two sips And I watch her Face flush And All of a sudden like I look over
and She's speaking really loud and like making jokes and I'm like I just knew that the drinks
and She's speaking really loud and like making jokes and I'm like I just knew that the drinks
were all laced with something um and She starts like Almost Being like belligerent a little bit
were all laced with something um and She starts like Almost Being like belligerent a little bit
but not like a Crazy way Just like really enjoying herself and I'm like That's not her That's not her
but not like a Crazy way Just like really enjoying herself and I'm like That's not her That's not her
She doesn't even want to be here like This is weird realize that I'm in the Studio with did
She doesn't even want to be here like This is weird realize that I'm in the Studio with did
and with and the off their shit and there's three other men an executive that works with kanye his
and con and the off their shit and there's three other men an executive that works with kanye his
engineer and his cousin and me I'm like you guys stop like stop stop and they're Getting
engineer and his cousin and me I'm like you guys stop like stop stop and they're Getting
to the point Where they have like ripped my shirt off and um like I'm like Almost fully exposed at
to the point Where they have like ripped my shirt off and um like I'm like Almost fully exposed at
this Point and they're both coming at Me And I'm like you guys seriously This is this isn't funny
this Point and they're both coming at Me And I'm like you guys seriously This is this isn't funny
Anymore And I look to my left Where his executive Is Like We know him Pretty well like we've been
Anymore And I look to my left Where his executive Is Like We know him Pretty well like we've been
around him a lot He's literally 3 Feet away from Me Like If I reached and he reached you like we
around him a lot He's literally 3 Feet away from Me Like If I reached and he reached you like we
could Touch like He's that Close And I look and I'm like Hey like I give that look Where
could Touch like He's that Close And I look and I'm like Hey like I give that look Where
I'm just like Come on like Step in like this isn't cool like You're a grown man like You're like 50
I'm just like Come on like Step in like this isn't cool like You're a grown man like You're like 50
years old I know you have a family like you know this isn't right like do something and This is
years old I know you have a family like you know this isn't right like do something and This is
the Part that for as long as I Live I will never fucking forget it isn't actually the aspect of
the Part that for as long as I Live I will never fucking forget it isn't actually the aspect of
Being sexually assaulted That's not What haunts me It's It's this It's as these two grown men
Being sexually assaulted That's not What haunts me It's It's this It's as these two grown men
were off I look over To This Man asking for help And I literally Mouth the word help and we lock
were off I look over To This Man asking for help And I literally Mouth the word help and we lock
eyes and he looks away I'm like Okay there's two more men in the room And I look to his engineer
eyes and he looks away I'm like Okay there's two more men in the room And I look to his engineer
next he was sitting right Right Next To him And I Know that He's married and he has he Just Had
next he was sitting right Right Next To him And I Know that He's married and he has he Just Had
a little baby girl and I'm like Okay He's Going To Do something and he looks down at his phone
a little baby girl and I'm like Okay He's Going To Do something and he looks down at his phone
and starts texting no one's Going To Do anything no one's Going To Do fucking anything and That's
and starts texting no one's Going To Do anything no one's Going To Do fucking anything and That's
When I was truly fucking scared trying to Get my And I realized That I was completely Alone And
When I was truly fucking scared trying to Get my And I realized That I was completely Alone And
um I closed My Eyes for a Second And I was like God help I think about this thing about putting complaints
um I closed My Eyes for a Second And I was like God help me opino sobre esto de poner denuncias
in public in programs and on social networks, complaints have to be made in court
en público en programas y en redes sociales las denuncias hay que ponerlas en el juzgado
I understand that the girl might be afraid to do it so that they wouldn't close doors on her or I
entiendo que la chica A lo mejor tendría miedo hacerlo para que no le cerraran puertas o yo que
know that something would happen to her, but I imagine that now that Didi is in jail, I understand that
sé que le pasara algo pero imagino que ahora que Didi está en la cárcel pues entiendo que
now she will take measures and this will be added to the causes that Didi has. It is inevitable to compare
ahora tomará medidas y esto se añadirá a las causas que tiene Didi es inevitable comparar
this case with that of Jeffrey Epin. By the way, you also have a series on this channel about
este caso con el de Jeffrey epin Por cierto también tenéis una serie en este canal sobre
that case and in fact I think it is very similar and it shows us once again how disgusting
ese caso y de hecho yo creo que sí que se parece muchísimo y nos muestra otra vez más qué asco
what is always behind the power. I think that this is a bit in all the elites,
no lo que hay detrás siempre del poder yo yo creo que esto está un poco en todas las élites
always these types of issues, no, and in the end the business world has a lot of
siempre este tipo de cuestiones no y es que al final el mundo de los negocios pues tiene mucha
mafia corruption, speaking half in quotes, okay, keep quiet, you have to be false, whatever it
mafia corrupción hablando medio entre comillas vale silencios tienes que ser falso sea lo que
is, eh, whether it's the world of Hollywood TV, even very powerful streamers, the
sea eh Ya sea el mundo de la tele de Hollywood incluso de los streamers muy potentes el mundo
business world in general is a bit like that. Well, I don't know if it's even comparable, let's not say it's not.
de los negocios en general es un poco así Bueno no sé si es incluso comparable no digamos que no está
At the same level, organizing the filth and filth of the hyper mega global elite level
Al mismo nivel organizar las porquerías y las guarrerías de la élite hiper mega global nivel
to be able to stop even the FBI than to organize parties for Hollywood perverts
poder frenar incluso al FBI que organizar fiestas para los pervertidos de Hollywood
On A Jet flying around the world Now it started On A tuesday somehow ended On The previous Sunday I
On A Jet flying around the world Now it started On A tuesday somehow ended On The previous Sunday I
don't know how he did that Now that I'm engaged I decided to Slow Down a little three days parties a
don't know how he did that Now that I'm engaged I decided to Slow Down a little three dy parties a
week Maybe Four not including the weekends One Day we went To This Party forg pimp Cup went to Had
week Maybe Four not including the weekends One Day we went To This Party forg pimp Cup went to Had
a pimp cup he Had a whole bunch of pimp ca pimp set It's hard to say which is more off the ha did
a pimp cup he Had a whole bunch of pimp c a pimp set It's hard to say which is more off the h a did
in the end jeffre was so afraid to speak or say anything that he could have said
al final jeffre tenía tanto miedo de hablar o largar todo lo que pudiera haber largado
that you know how he ended up seeing if it is true that the people who would want to silence him in the case
que ya sabéis Cómo acabó a ver si que es verdad que la gente que querría silenciarlo en el caso
of Didi would not be the same in any case to Didi I wanted to silence him, people like Will me LeBron
de Didi no sería lo mismo en todo caso a Didi lo quería silenciar gente como Will me LeBron
Janes Leonardo DiCaprio are not people with as much power as what Jeffrey
janes Leonardo DiCaprio no son gente con tanto poder como lo que que tenía lo alto el Jeffrey
Esting had at the top, but it is true that there are many people who are afraid of him, there are also many other people
esting pero sí que es verdad que hay mucha gente que le tiene miedo también hay otra mucha gente
who really want him. for all the bad things she has done in life Didi She received the
que le tiene muchas ganas por todas las cosas malas que ha hecho en la vida Didi Recibió la
first complaint for rape and abuse in 1990 then another in 1991 then in 1999 another for harassment
primera denuncia por violación y abusos en 1990 luego otra en 1991 luego en 1999 otra por acoso
and the nightclub shooting with Jennifer Lopez in 2003 another for sexual abuse in 2012 She blew
y el tiroteo de la discoteca con Jennifer López en 2003 otra por abuso sexual en el 2012 hizo
up her ex Kid Coody's boyfriend's car with explosives. You have this in a video. I
volar con explosivos el coche del novio de su ex Kid coody esto lo tenéis en un vídeo os lo
remind you of it in 2015 for assault. In 2018, she hit Casey. In 2022, the complaint from producer
recuerdo en el 2015 por agresión el 2018 golpeó a Casey en el 2022 la denuncia del productor
John for abuse. And in this last year, three other complaints. for sexual abuse and we are talking
John por abuso Y en este último año otras tres denuncias por abuso sexual y estamos hablando
about complaints from victims who have dared to report there are many others who speak and who
de denuncias de víctimas que se han atrevido a denunciar hay otras muchas que hablan y que se
know each other from behind that they are bz populis who have not reported Eh This without also counting the issue of
conocen por detrás que son bz populis que no han denunciado Eh Esto sin contar también el tema del
carrying weapons and the alleged involvement in the murder of Tupac And then how has he gotten rid of
porte de armas y la supuesta implicación en el asesinato de Tupac Y entonces cómo se ha Librado
all these years of so many things, well, the money is the power. I read the conditions that he had
todos estos años de tantas cosas pues la pasta eh el poder os Leo las condiciones que él había
offered to the judges in this last week for his conditional release while
ofrecido a los jueces en esta última semana para que le eran la libertad condicional mientras que
the trial was being held. case and not the bail 100 million dollars not having visits from women at home
se juzgaba el caso y no la fianza 100 millones de dólares no tener visitas de mujeres en casa
who were not his service employees his relatives his mansion and his mother's mansion
que no fueran sus empleadas del servicio sus familiares su mansión y la mansión de su madre
as collateral security cameras with real-time police surveillance in his house and GPS tracking
como garantía cámaras de seguridad con vigilancia de la policía en tiempo real en su casa y rastreo
alcohol and drug test when he wanted to give up his entire family's
por GPS test de alcoholemia y droga cuando se apeteciera ser renuncia de toda su familia de
passports, his is already canceled for obvious reasons and even sell his plane to
los pasaportes el de él ya está cancelado por obvias razones y hasta vender su avión para
show that he did not intend to gamble. The move here is that the issue of peace Dad It is not only
demostrar que no pretendía jugarse La Movida aquí es que el tema de paz Dad no es solamente
for reasons of flight risk but he is not allowed to leave jail so that he does not try to
por cuestiones de riesgo de fuga sino que no se le permite salir de la cárcel para que no intente
blackmail or offer something so that the Witnesses or possible witnesses can change the version and not
chantajear o ofrecer algo para que los Testigos o posibles testigos puedan cambiar la versión y no
only with a plan to try to make agreements but You already know that Paz Dad has a very
solamente con pcta en plan intentar hacer acuerdos sino que ya sabéis que Paz Dad pues tiene mucha
good relationship with gangster gangs since the 90s. I think you will agree with me that
buena relación con pandillas gangsters desde los años 90 yo creo que estaréis de acuerdo conmigo en
the turning point at which people took a turn was if there was someone who did not believe that this
que el punto de inflexión en el que la gente dio un girito si había alguien que no creía que este
man had been able to do all these things and I only thought that they would be conspiracies and
hombre había podido hacer todas estas cosas y solamente pensaba que serían conspiraciones y
things that are said about famous people was the moment in which the video was made public where he hits
cosas que se hablan de los famosos fue el momento en el que se hizo público el vídeo donde golpea a
casy We also have a video on this topic, I recommend that you watch it But well, I said it,
casy También tenemos un vídeo de este tema os recomiendo que lo veáis Pero bueno lo he dicho
okay, there is a playlist with all the things and we are completely up to date. It is always
vale hay una lista de reproducción con todas las cosas y estamos completamente al día siempre es
true that no matter how many testimonies there are, there are many people who talk, it is not the case. same when there is
verdad que por muchos testimonios que hay hay mucha gente que hable no es lo mismo cuando hay
a super graphic illustrative video in such a flagrant way and it is the same thing that we talked about At that
un vídeo ilustrativo super gráfico de una forma tan flagrante y es lo mismo que hablamos En aquel
moment when the video was published Not if this is done to you in the hallways of a hotel, what is it
momento cuando se publicó el vídeo No si esto te lo hacen los pasillos de un hotel que es lo
that does to you when you don't believe that it they are recording is that before this video many
que te hace cuando no se cree que lo están grabando es que antes de este vídeo muchas
things could be like urban legends stories no eh creepy legs I already told you no
cosas podían ser como leyendas urbanas historias no eh creepy patas ya te digo no creencias de
conspiracy beliefs but no no that video shows that eh what is said about it could be true
conspiraciones pero no no ese vídeo demuestra que eh lo que se dice de él podría ser verdad
almost everything if not everything goes The mayor of New York Eric Adams, the same one who gave the key to the
casi todo si no todo vale el alcalde de Nueva York Eric Adams el mismo que le entregó la llave de la
city to Didi on the same day her album came out, most likely with the intention of promoting it, today
ciudad a Didi el mismo día que salió su álbum muy seguramente con la intención de promocionarlo hoy
has precisely been accused by a prosecutor of corruption. It is not ruled out that in addition
precisamente ha sido acusado por un fiscal por corrupción no se descarta que además
to the case of corruption this man has also included the investigation of the
del caso de corrupción este hombre se ha también incluido la investigación del caso de
did case and to finish today's case we will return to touch a little
did y para terminar el de hoy volver a tocar un poco
on the topic of Jennifer López who seems to be shaking if the
el tema de Jennifer López que parece ser que estaría temblando si se vuelve a remover el
case in which she was involved is removed again and for which Didi almost got
caso en el que ella estuvo involucrada y por el que Didi casi consigue que acabe
Jennifer Lopez to end with a criminal record that this would probably have ruined her
Jennifer Lopez con antecedentes penales que esto probablemente hubiera hecho que se arruinara la
career
carrera
puon of wenderson nowt during the trial fenderson testified That colmes Was armed the Night of the
puon of wenderson nowt during the trial fenderson testified That colmes Was armed the Night of the
Shooting at Club New York and later pressured him to claim ownership of a pistol police Found
Shooting at Club New York and later pressured him to claim ownership of a pistol police Found
When they pulled over coles Lincoln Navigator as it fled the Shooting and Just Jennifer Lopez
When they pulled over coles Lincoln Navigator as it fled the Shooting and Just Jennifer Lopez
Who was in the Navigator When It was stopped by police an officer testified that everyone in the
Who was in the Navigator When It was stopped by police an officer testified that everyone in the
suv was ordered to put their hands on the vehicle but Lopez walked away saying She was going home
suv was ordered to put their hands on the vehicle but Lopez walked away saying She was going home
as She was Being detained a gun was discovered in the vehicle at that Point A sergeant On The
as She was Being detained a gun was discovered in the vehicle at that Point A sergeant On The
I do obviously believe that this gun was not Jennifer López's and the move is
yo sí creo evidentemente que este arma no era de Jennifer López y la movida es
that however and surprisingly It seems that to this day Jennifer Lopez still has
que sin embargo y sorprendentemente Parece ser que a día de hoy Jennifer López sigue teniendo
a good vibe with Didi, she even continues to be at some parties and collaborating with him
buen rollo con Didi incluso Sigue estando en algunas fiestas y colaborando con él
and Well in that case you already know that this man paid the price. The rapper
y Bueno en ese caso ya sabéis que el pato lo pagó este hombre El rapero
Shan who to this day despite having served the punishment, he continues to say that
Shan que a día de hoy a pesar de haber cumplido el castigo sigue diciendo que
he is innocent, this is a curious case that I think will give much more to talk about than the
él es inocente esto es un caso curioso que yo creo que dará mucho más que hablar sa que k
record executive and criminal with Víctor but an expert in the Didi industry, he stated that
ejecutivo discográfico y delincuente con Víctor pero conocedor de la industria de Didi afirmó que
Jennifer López's breakup with Ben aflex It is very possibly due to the things that she hides from
la ruptura de Jennifer López con Ben aflex se debe muy posiblemente a las cosas que ella oculta de
Didi vide J doing this J doing that they know the
Didi vide J doing this J doing that they know the
J or Whatever his Life
J or Whatever his Life
according to this man Jennifer López would appear in some of the tapes that have been found in
según este hombre Jennifer López aparecería en algunas de las cintas que se han encontrado en la
Didi's house, this is not He is saying only he, I think in the previous video we actually
casa de Didi esto no lo está diciendo Solamente él eh creo que en el vídeo anterior de hecho
mentioned that I don't know if it was F who also mentioned it so well as the
mencionamos que no sé si fue F el que también lo mencionó así que bueno conforme vayan pasando los
days go by I will inform you important family that you subscribe to the Channel so that I
días os iré informando familia importante que os suscribáis al Canal para que yo me
realize that you like this type of video and you want us to continue here at the top of the
dé cuenta que os gusta este tipo de vídeo y que queréis que continuemos aquí al pie del
canyon that you subscribe that I press the like button that you share the video on your
cañón que os suscribáis que pulsé el botón de like que compartáis el vídeo en vuestras redes
social networks WhatsApp Twitter Facebook and whoever wants to collaborate with the channel you have a button
sociales WhatsApp Twitter Facebook y quien quiera colaborar con el canal tenéis un botón
that says super Thank you where you can highlight your comment by making any donation
que pone super Gracias donde podéis destacar vuestro comentario haciendo cualquier donación
I send you a very strong kiss see you tomorrow the day after tomorrow in a next video and bye bye
os mando un beso muy fuerte nos vemos mañana mañana pasado en un próximo vídeo y chao chao
handsome for
guapos for